[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "Why did Jovan Belcher need a high-powered hand gun?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "Jovan", "Belcher", "need", "a", "high-powered", "hand", "gun", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Well, he didn't need a -- any hand gun to kill to murder his wife and leave the poor baby as an orphan.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "did", "n't", "need", "a", "--", "any", "hand", "gun", "to", "kill", "to", "murder", "his", "wife", "and", "leave", "the", "poor", "baby", "as", "an", "orphan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jovan Belcher"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "Well, I'm assuming most hand guns are high powered, right?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "assuming", "most", "hand", "guns", "are", "high", "powered", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJS", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "VBN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "So what you mean -- so you call it high powered handgun by which you mean a normal handgun and I don't know why he owned a handgun.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "what", "you", "mean", "--", "so", "you", "call", "it", "high", "powered", "handgun", "by", "which", "you", "mean", "a", "normal", "handgun", "and", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "why", "he", "owned", "a", "handgun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "At what point do you say in America, enough guns, actually what we need to do is reduce the number of guns?", "question_tokens": ["At", "what", "point", "do", "you", "say", "in", "America", ",", "enough", "guns", ",", "actually", "what", "we", "need", "to", "do", "is", "reduce", "the", "number", "of", "guns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "121203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Why don't we try 300 million?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "n't", "we", "try", "300", "million", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Well, you see, you want to confiscate all guns in the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "see", ",", "you", "want", "to", "confiscate", "all", "guns", "in", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "What is your take on it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "take", "on", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "It's mind-boggling to me.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "mind-boggling", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "What is your view of what he said and his right to say it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "of", "what", "he", "said", "and", "his", "right", "to", "say", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Well, again, there's a time and a place.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "again", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "time", "and", "a", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "Short of bringing you out of retirement, what should they be doing?", "question_tokens": ["Short", "of", "bringing", "you", "out", "of", "retirement", ",", "what", "should", "they", "be", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Well, they ought to be dealing with this on the up-and-up instead of dealing the way they are.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "ought", "to", "be", "dealing", "with", "this", "on", "the", "up-and-up", "instead", "of", "dealing", "the", "way", "they", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "EX", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "Confident?", "question_tokens": ["Confident", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Now you're talking about some good football there, buddy.", "answer_tokens": ["Now", "you", "'re", "talking", "about", "some", "good", "football", "there", ",", "buddy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "The law is being changed to ensure that whoever the firstborn child is, boy or girl, will automatically become king or queen, but it's not actually a done deal yet, is it?", "question_tokens": ["The", "law", "is", "being", "changed", "to", "ensure", "that", "whoever", "the", "firstborn", "child", "is", ",", "boy", "or", "girl", ",", "will", "automatically", "become", "king", "or", "queen", ",", "but", "it", "'s", "not", "actually", "a", "done", "deal", "yet", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJR", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "CC", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "No, it's not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Is it literally the first one out is the heir?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "literally", "the", "first", "one", "out", "is", "the", "heir", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "Well, like you say, if this legislation comes into play, which I suspect it will ahead of the birth, then yes, if the firstborn, the first twin to birth is a girl, then she will take precedence over either the sister or the brother.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "like", "you", "say", ",", "if", "this", "legislation", "comes", "into", "play", ",", "which", "I", "suspect", "it", "will", "ahead", "of", "the", "birth", ",", "then", "yes", ",", "if", "the", "firstborn", ",", "the", "first", "twin", "to", "birth", "is", "a", "girl", ",", "then", "she", "will", "take", "precedence", "over", "either", "the", "sister", "or", "the", "brother", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "People call it acute morning sickness or whatever, but it's a bit worse than that, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["People", "call", "it", "acute", "morning", "sickness", "or", "whatever", ",", "but", "it", "'s", "a", "bit", "worse", "than", "that", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "It is worse than just typical morning sickness.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "worse", "than", "just", "typical", "morning", "sickness", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RBS", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "CC", "RB", ",", "VBG", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "Does it increase the potential risk of a miscarriage?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "increase", "the", "potential", "risk", "of", "a", "miscarriage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Well, it does increase the possible risk of having a baby prematurely, although if you look across the board, most babies are born perfectly healthy so it's a small increase in that sort of condition but typically if it's going to be treated well and again, lasting just a few weeks, then everything should go pretty well after that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "does", "increase", "the", "possible", "risk", "of", "having", "a", "baby", "prematurely", ",", "although", "if", "you", "look", "across", "the", "board", ",", "most", "babies", "are", "born", "perfectly", "healthy", "so", "it", "'s", "a", "small", "increase", "in", "that", "sort", "of", "condition", "but", "typically", "if", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "treated", "well", "and", "again", ",", "lasting", "just", "a", "few", "weeks", ",", "then", "everything", "should", "go", "pretty", "well", "after", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "And do you see again -- I know you've done so much on this, but do you see a potential parallel here with him?", "question_tokens": ["And", "do", "you", "see", "again", "--", "I", "know", "you", "'ve", "done", "so", "much", "on", "this", ",", "but", "do", "you", "see", "a", "potential", "parallel", "here", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "Well, you know, I think a lot of people are certainly looking that way.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "think", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "are", "certainly", "looking", "that", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "Given that both sides know where they need to move, why the games?", "question_tokens": ["Given", "that", "both", "sides", "know", "where", "they", "need", "to", "move", ",", "why", "the", "games", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Well, it's not clear that both sides know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "clear", "that", "both", "sides", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "You're calling Reid as well?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "calling", "Reid", "as", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "Oh, yes, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Reid"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "121203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "How did you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "Standing on the stage at the White House looking out at my buddies that I served in combat with, all the brass in the military, two families that had lost their sons that night that I was being awarded this medal for, it was very bittersweet.", "answer_tokens": ["Standing", "on", "the", "stage", "at", "the", "White", "House", "looking", "out", "at", "my", "buddies", "that", "I", "served", "in", "combat", "with", ",", "all", "the", "brass", "in", "the", "military", ",", "two", "families", "that", "had", "lost", "their", "sons", "that", "night", "that", "I", "was", "being", "awarded", "this", "medal", "for", ",", "it", "was", "very", "bittersweet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "What is your view about gun control in America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "about", "gun", "control", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "I absolutely love the Second Amendment.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "absolutely", "love", "the", "Second", "Amendment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "What is life going to be like for you now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "life", "going", "to", "be", "like", "for", "you", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "Life's exciting.", "answer_tokens": ["Life", "'s", "exciting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]